rentsfnow.com 2017-08-10

# Privacy Policy – RentSFNow

This website and any affiliated websites (collectively, “Website”), and their contents and information, are the property of RentSFNow (“RentSFNow”). Any use of the Website constitutes acceptance of the terms of the following Privacy Policy, including any amendments and/or modifications or revisions thereof, which may be made by RentSFNow at any time in its sole discretion.

 **COLLECTION OF INFORMATION**  
Our servers automatically collect certain internet traffic-related information from each visitor to the Website. That information includes the name of the visitor’s internet service provider, IP address, the date and time of access this site, the domain name (but not e-mail addresses), the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages visitors access or visit, and information volunteered by visitors. For example, when you request information through the Website, we might ask you for information that will allow us to respond. You may elect to provide us with information that identifies you (e.g., name, e-mail address, mailing address, zip code and telephone number). You may also elect to provide additional information to us by sending or responding to e-mails. We may use this information to help us improve this site or to perform services. We also may provide such information to our employees, contractors, agents, and designees to the extent necessary to enable them to perform services on RentSFNow’ behalf.

 **COOKIES**  
Information from Cookies and Similar Technologies.  
We and our service providers collect information through the use of “cookies” and similar technologies to understand how you interact with our Website. Cookies are small text files that web servers place on your device; they are designed to store basic information and to help websites and apps recognize your browser. We may use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie disappears after you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be accessed every time you use our Website. We also use cookies for data analytics purposes, including from Google Analytics. You can find more information on how Google uses data from these cookies at [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners). You should consult your web browser to modify your cookie settings. Please note that if you delete or choose not to accept cookies from us, you may be missing out on certain features of our Website.

 **CONTACT**  
If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us an e-mail at the e-mail address provided in the e-mailed materials. If you supply us with your postal address on-line, you may receive periodic postal or e-mailings from us with information on our services, news about RentSFNow, and updates or announcement about upcoming events or activities. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by sending us written correspondence to that effect to the mailing address or e-mail address provided in those materials.

 **LINKS TO THIRD-PARTY SITES**  
This Website may contain links to third-party websites. We are not and cannot be responsible for the contents, information, security or privacy practices of such other websites. Please note that this Privacy Policy applies solely to this Website. We encourage you to ensure that you read the privacy statements of all the destination web sites which you visit. If you elect to link to third-party websites, you may receive cookies from those third-parties. We do not control these third-party cookies, and they are not subject to this Privacy Policy.

 **OTHER**  
RentSFNow does not sell, trade, or rent any personal information to others. We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies. We are committed to protecting the privacy of the users of the Website. All information which we obtain is held in a secured database. We are not and cannot be responsible for the security of any such database.

If you have any questions with respect to our privacy policies and procedures, please feel free to contact us at [info@rentsfnow.com](mailto:info@rentsfnow.com).
